cute.
かわいい
sorry.
ごめんなさい
It's okay, it's okay.
いいよ、大丈夫
a bit.
少し
That's right.
そうだよね
Someone is saying it.
誰か言ってるね
is that so.
そうですか
Who is it?
誰なの?
Not told?
言われない?
Hmm.
うーん
I won't be told.
言われないです
why?
なんで?
Why what are you doing?
なんでなんでしてるの?
Why did you do that?
なんでしたの?
no...
いや...
Peri-peri,
ペリペリがね、
He dresses like this with his shoulders exposed.
こんな 肩出してる 格好するんだ
Yes, I will.
はい、します
It's summer after all.
夏だしね
I agree.
そうですね
You can look good in summer.
夏の格好できるし
Hey, this is it. What kind of string is this?
ちょっとこれさ、 これ紐、 何の紐?
It's underwear.
下着です
Is it okay if I take this out?
これ出しちゃっていいの?
picture?
え?
I don't know.
分からない
I don't know?
分からない?
I'll continue to do my best in this kind of entertainment.I'm passionate about it.
ちゃんとさ、これからもさ、 そういう芸能を頑張るの パッショ
I have to study N.
ン を勉強しないと
that's right.
そうです
It suits you though.
似合ってるけどね
Do you like it a little?
ちょっと 好き?
I couldn't do it at all during this time.
この間全然できなかったの
Because I put it in.
入れしちゃったから
I really like it.
本当に好きなんだ
Oh no.
いやぁ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Yeah.
うん
It's so cute.
すごい可愛いよ
This is what I wanted to photograph.
こういうのがさ、 撮りたかったんだよね
During this time.
この間
This kind of thing is amazing.
こういうの、すごい
Just do this right away, are you dressed like this so I can show you?
すぐこうやってさ、 見せられるようにこういう服になってるの?
That's right.
そうなんですよね
It's a Weberander.
ウェベランダーでしょ
Yeah.
うん
Just do it yourself, this.
ちょっと自分でさ、これ
Hold your chest and let me show you.
胸をもってさ、 見せてもらおう
This is difficult.
これは難い
Gravure practice.
グラビアの練習
That's fine, right?
いいでしょ
I want to be buried there.
埋もれたい、そこに
There's someone you admire.
憧れの人がいるんだよね
yes.
はい
This is Ai Shibasaki.
柴崎愛衣さんです
It's a little similar.
ちょっと似てるもんね
Experience.
体験とか
I'm aiming for it.
目指してます
do your best.
頑張って
Erotic, Erororimuchimuchiken.
エロ、 エロロリムチムチケン
Are you really caring?
ちゃんと気遣ってるの?
Beth beh.
ベスベー
A little smell.
少し匂い
a bit?
少し?
I agree.
そうですね
It's like applying oil.
オイル塗ったりって感じで
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Every day?
毎中で?
that's right.
そうです
I'll go paint it.
塗りに行ってあげる
Is it true?
本当ですか?
I'll go out and paint.
塗りに遊びに行ってあげる
Now.
今 で
Are you happy?
嬉しいでしょ?
I'm having a little trouble.
ちょっと困っちゃう
I'll put my feet up.
足上げちゃう
fault.
あら
Doing naughty poses.
えっちなポーズしてる
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I have to do a pose like this
こういうポーズでもしなきゃいけないで
Sho.
しょ
I have to do a sexy pose too
セ クシーなポーズでもしなきゃいけ
do not have.
ない
Did you use it today?
今日 使ったでしょ?
Yes, I used it.
はい、使った
Was it Hampis?
ハンピースだった?
yes.
はい
Well then,
じゃあ、
Let's touch it.
触 ってみよう
picture?
え?
Isn't this connected?
これ繋がってるんじゃないの?
yes.
はい
Which is more difficult?
どっちが難しい?
Which one?
どっちなの?
From tomorrow?
明日から?
I keep touching this.
ずっと触っちゃわれるね、これ
What do you think?
どうですか?
It's impossible, it's impossible.
無理無理無理だね
Do you want it at home?
家に欲しい?
Unreasonable, unreasonable
無理無理無
reason.
理
Your boyfriend also touches this, right?
彼 氏もこれ触るでしょ?
yes.
はい
Hey.
ねえ
I already left it here.
もうここに置いておいた
So, is it okay to be my boyfriend?
じゃあ、彼氏でいいですか?
Hmm.
う ーん
strict.
厳しい
strict?
厳しい?
So, what is your second name, your boyfriend?
じゃあ、第二名は彼氏は?
Thailand.
タイ
what?
なに?
About 10?
10くらい?
Number nine: I'll kill you.
9番目は、 末殺するわ
Then there will be a collision, right?
そしたら衝突でしょ?
scared.
怖い
scared?
怖い?
Well then,
じゃあ、
You have to get used to the camera.
カ メラに慣れないといけないじゃん
Sit here.
座って、ここ
picture?
え?
what?
なに?
You like eating, right?
食べるの好きでしょ?
Yes, I like it.
はい、好きです
It's chewy.
もちもちだもんね
what happened?
どうしたの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Aren't you embarrassed?
恥ずかしくないの?
You look amazing.
すごい 格好してるね
Have you come?
来てきちゃった?
Have you ever brushed your teeth?
歯磨きしたことあるでしょ?
a,
あ、
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
I'll put it out.
出すよ